杰西卡
Jessica.
杰西卡  快点  我们得走了
Jessica. Come on. We gotta go.
-再不走就迟到了  -我不舒服
- Move it or lose it, sister. - I don't feel good.
-你没发烧呀  -我肚子疼
- Mmm. You don't feel warm. - My stomach hurts.
亲爱的  如果你没发烧...
Well, honey, if you don't have a fever-
我不想去学校  我可以在家学习
I don't wanna go to school. I can do my work at home.
杰西卡  怎么了
Jessica, what's wrong?
大家都讨厌我
Everybody hates me.
他们不会讨厌你的
Oh, they don't hate you.
他们都不了解你
They don't even know you
因为他们愚蠢得对你产生了成见
because they're too ignorant to try.
-我讨厌我自己  -杰西卡  别这么说
- I hate myself. - Jessica, don't say that.
亲爱的  看着我  看着我
Oh, honey. Look at me. Look at me.
你是个优秀的  漂亮的小女孩
You are a wonderful, beautiful little girl.
-别让几个坏家伙  -几个吗  是整个班
- Don't let a few bad apples - A few? Try my whole class.
记得那个故事吗
Remember the story where the guy
有个人一直说自己讨厌鸡蛋和火腿
keeps saying that he hates green eggs and ham?
最后他才发现其实他喜欢
And then at the end he realized he really loved them?
总有一天他们会知道你是个多么好的孩子
One day, they're gonna realize what a great kid you really are.
你只要做自己就好了  而且不要放弃
You just gotta be like Sam-l-Am. And don't give up.
好吧
Okay.
就这样  继续
That's it. Keep goin".
不错  杰西卡  你做得很好
Good. Nice. You're doin'great, Jessica. You're doin'great.
赛斯
Hey. Hey, Seth.
-你想被罚坐冷板凳吗  -不
- You wanna spend the rest of class sittin' on the bench? - No.
继续  杰西卡  还剩40秒
Keep goin', Jess. You got 40 more seconds.
我胳膊疼
My arm hurts.
加油  坚持一下  你能行的
Come on. Tough it up. You can do it. You can do it.
-我胸口疼  -你以为地板不疼吗
- My chest hurts. - How do you think the ground feels?
赛斯  罚跑两圈  再见
Hey, Seth. Two laps. Bye.
杰西卡  只是一点小疼痛
Hey, Jess. It's just a stitch.
保持呼吸节奏  你能行的
Okay? Just... keep breathin". You got it.
我不行了
I can't.
只剩10秒了  你能行的
Only 10 more seconds. You got it.
杰西卡  杰西卡
Jessica? Jessica?
杰西卡
Jessica!
天啊  快去办公室叫帕森斯老师  快
Oh, my God. Hey, go to the office. Get Miss Parsons. Now!
我在芬利小学的操场上
I'm on the playground at Finley Elementary.
有个学生心脏病发作了
One of my students is havin' a heart attack.
她10岁  你以为我不知道吗
Yeah, she's 10. Don't you think I know that?
赶紧派辆该死的救护车来
Just send the damn ambulance.
拜托  醒醒  拜托了宝贝儿
Come on. Wake up. Come on, sweetie.
本德尔医生  请拨分机2870
Dr. Bender, call extension 2870.
你见过因为穿孔而感染的阴囊吗
You ever seen an infected pierced scrotum?
没  不过我倒是先看看什么人会这么做
Um, no, but I know a few people on whom I'd like to see it happen.
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
要是想找疼的话  应该穿阴茎
Well, if pain's what you're after, the penis is really the way to go.
-我推荐阴茎钉  -我们说正经的
- I'd recommend the apadravya. - We're not talking.
不是挺正经的吗
Oh. It sounded like we were.
不  你总是绕开话题
No, you're attempting to avoid talking
因为你知道我要谈什么
because you know what I wanna talk about.
-乳头吗  -你得炒掉你的人其中一个
- Nipples? - You need to get rid of one of your people.
当然  等我做完绩效考核
Absolutely. As soon as I do performance reviews.
然后再复审一下考核结果
And then review the reviews, of course.
没有调查就没有发言权  你知道的
A decision like this can't be made without proper, you know, review.
应该不会超过一个月  可能两个月
Shouldn't take longer than a month, maybe two.
最多四个月  除非变得复杂不堪
Four at the most, unless it gets complicated.
没门
There's no way outta this.
你最好速战速决
You might as well get it over with as fast as you can,
快刀斩乱麻
like ripping off a Band-Aid.
可要搞定的不是一团乱麻
Only instead of a two-cent piece of tape and gauze,
而是一个人
it's a human being.
-说得你很在乎似的  -说得你不在乎似的
- Like you care. - Like you don't.
给你一周时间  搞定这事
You have a week. Get it done.
我们有个从兰基威兹医生那转来的病人
We have a referral from Dr. Lenkiewicz.
-我不认识他  -他认识你
- Don't know him. - He knows you.
-什么问题  -心脏病发作
- What's the problem? - Heart attack.
-真不认识他  -病人才10岁
- Definitely don't know him. - The patient's 10.
10岁不应该有心脏病  肯定是弄错了
Ten-year-olds do not have heart attacks. It's gotta be a mistake.
当然  最简单的解释是
Right. Simplest explanation is
她在撒谎  她其实40岁了
she's a 40-year-old lying about her age.
说不定是个想装嫩的女演员
Maybe an actress trying to hang on.
我是说可能检查出问题了
I meant maybe the tests were wrong.
急诊室也这么想的
That's what the E.R. Thought.
三次肌酸激酶检测都是阳性
Three C.K. -M.B. 's were positive.
心电图显示ST段抬高  确实是心脏病
The E.K.G. shows classic signs of S. T. Elevation. It's a heart attack.
她病态肥胖  所以有这些心脏病征兆
She's morbidly obese. The "Morbid" Part of that raises alarms.
拜托  要吃成心脏病得好几十年呢
Come on. It takes decades to eat your way into a heart attack.
但自杀用不了几十年
Doesn't take decades to kill yourself.
如果我那么胖  我宁肯服毒自尽了
If I was that fat, I'd be pretty tempted to knock back a bottle of pills.
不是服药过量
It's not a drug overdose.
疲劳  肌肉疼痛和无法集中精神
The fatigue, muscle pain and difficulty concentrating
这些症状已经持续一年多了
have been bothering her for over a year.
这是因为她的体重  还有抑郁
That's because of her weight, her depression.
五个儿科医生  两个营养学家
That's what five pediatricians, two nutritionists
和一个心理学家都这么说
and a psychologist said.
心脏发病说明他们肯定遗漏了什么
The heart attack would seem to indicate that they missed something.
应该是遗传因素吧
It's gotta be something genetic.
是不是X代谢综合征
What about metabolic syndrome "X"?
抗胰岛素吗
Insulin resistance?
X综合征可以导致中风
Syndrome "X" Could cause a stroke.
但我没听过还有心脏病的
I don't know about a heart attack.
如果血压够高的话  可能的
It could, if her blood pressure was high enough.
很有可能  看看她的体重就知道了
Which is likely, considering her weight.
和症状相符  我同意
Fits the symptoms. Me likee.
做一个高胰岛素-正常血糖钳夹检测
Do a hyperinsulinemic euglycemic clamp.
对了  还有件事
Oh, and one more thing.
上级通知我  这周内我得炒掉你们中的一个
I've been told that I gotta get rid of one of you guys by the end of the week.
新官上任三把火  你们明白的
New sheriff. Belt tightening. You know how it goes.
行了  去吧
Okay. Carry on.
他又在戏弄我们了
Some kind of game.
豪斯自创的整人节目
House's own version of Punk'd.
不是豪斯  是沃格勒
It's not House. It's Vogler.
不能让这事影响我们  我们得团结一致
We can't let it get to us. We've gotta stick together.
为什么
Why?
难道你觉得我们该为此斗得你死我活吗
Are you suggesting we start slashing each other's throats?
我是说这是个零和博弈
I'm suggesting it's a zero-sum game.
你输了我就赢了
Your loss is my win.
团队合作好像没什么好处
That's not conducive to team play.
豪斯就是想看好戏
Which is what House seems to want.
我同意卡梅隆
Look, I'm with Cameron.
虽然可能不是个好主意
It may be a bad strategy,
但我不想满足豪斯的看客心理
but I don't wanna give House that satisfaction.
走啦  孩子还病着呢
Come on. Sick kid, remember?
她有糖尿病吗
She's diabetic?
不  但差不多
No, but it's similar.
X代谢综合征的病人对胰岛素没有反应
M.S.X. Patients don't respond normally to insulin,
所以他们的身体产生了过多的糖
which causes their body to create too much,
导致一系列的代谢异常
and that leads to metabolic abnormalities.
我们会做个测试来确诊
We're going to do a test to be sure,
但这个测试有一定的风险
but there are certain dangers.
这个病可以...  治疗吗
Is this... thing treatable?
可以通过适当的饮食和锻炼控制病情
It's controllable through proper diet and exercise.
等等  杰西卡的饮食已经很健康了
Wait. Jessica already eats right,
而且她每天都锻炼
and she exercises every day.
我知道你们看过一些营养学家
I know you've already seen several nutritionists-
而且我们采纳了他们所有的建议
And we've done everything they've recommended.
我明白  但...
I understand, but-
为什么你们医生就没有人能忽略她的肥胖呢
Why can't any of you doctors see past her weight?
如果饮食和锻炼可以治疗的话
If diet and exercise are the treatment,
那这个诊断肯定是错的
then the diagnosis is wrong.
有可能
It might be.
但确诊的唯一方法是你允许我们做这个检测
But the only way we'll know is if you let us do this test.
很难受  特别是晚上
It's really bad, especially at night.
好像心里着火了似的
It's like my heart is on fire. Like it's, um-
我也说不清楚  好像...
Oh, I don't know. Like, uh-
-灼热  -没错
- Burning? - Exactly.
听上去像是...  烧心
sounds almost like... heartburn.
-你能给我点什么吗  -给你本十万个为什么?
- So, can you give me somethin'? - Like a thesaurus?
什么
What?
你没在产前检查时提过这个症状吧
I take it you never mentioned this during any of your prenatal visits.
产前
Prenatal?
我没怀孕
I'm not pregnant.
不好意思  除非你是听诊器
Sorry, you don't get to make that call
否则你没资格这么说  统一规定
unless you have a stethoscope. Union rules.
我知道我怀没怀孕
I know when I'm pregnant, all right?
我都有六个小孩了
I have six kids.
所以我丈夫做了输精管切除术
That's why my husband had a vasectomy,
而且我们还用安全套
and we use condoms.
输精管被切了可以自己恢复
Vasectomies can reverse themselves.
安全套可能会破
Condoms break.
好吧  女人就该长成这样
Okay. This... is what a woman is supposed to look like.
我们不能只是皮包骨头
Okay? We're not just skin and bones.
我们有...  肉肉  有...  曲线
We have... flesh. We have... curves.
你有个小小人在你身体里
You have little people inside you.
好吧  好吧
Okay, okay.
对不起  我想我可能被媒体
I'm sorry. I guess I must have just been brainwashed by the media...
和多年的医学教育给洗脑了
and all those years of medical training.
-没错  -趁护士给你抽血
- Damn right. - I'll see if I can
我去试着帮你找点抗酸剂
find some antacids while the nurse gets some blood.
抽血  为什么
Blood? Why?
烧心  我们得确定它不会传染
The heartburn. Gotta make sure it's not... spreading.
我不要
I don't want to.
这项测试涉及一些十分精确的测量手段
The test involves some pretty precise measurements.
如果我们不知道你的精确体重
If we don't know exactly how much you weigh,
我们就无法得到正确结果
we won't get the right answers.
告诉你个秘密
Let me tell you a secret.
我在你这么大的时候也很胖
When I was your age, I was heavy too.
你超过了100磅吗
Were you over a hundred?
胖多了  邻居的小孩都叫我"里让"
Way over. Kids in my neighborhood used to call me "Rerun."
-里让  -他是电视里一个很胖的人
- Rerun? - He was a heavy guy from TV.
我装作很喜欢这个外号  其实并不是
I used to pretend I liked it, but I didn't.
那你怎么瘦下来的
How come you're not heavy anymore?
九年级的时候  长高了5英寸
Ninth grade, grew five inches.
所有问题都迎刃而解
Everything kind of evened out.
-你觉得我也会那样吗  -当然
- You think that'll happen to me? - Well, yeah.
你妈妈挺高的
Your mom's tall,
你在这个年龄又偏矮
and you are a little short for your age.
可能马上就要猛长了
Probably spring right up.
肥胖可不是你长着长着就没了
Obesity isn't something you just grow out of.
你没见过婴儿吗
I take it you've never seen a baby?
她可不是婴儿  她都10岁了
She's not a baby. She's 10.
你以为让她觉得自己是个废物就能帮到她吗
And you figure making her feel like crap would do her a world of good?
当然  如果能让她不再成天躺在沙发上的话
Yeah, if it gets her off the couch.
我确信她承受的压力已经够大了
I'm sure she's already under enough pressure.
肯定不是她妈妈给的
Not from Mummy.
社会的方方面面都表明  苗条才能成功
Everything in society tells us we have to be thin to be successful.
才不是
No.
社会只是告诉大家纤瘦比较有吸引力
Society tells you you have to be thin to be attractive.
知道吗
And guess what?
苗条和吸引力就是同义词
That's what attractive means,
大家都喜欢观摩你
that society likes looking at you.
我觉得应该告诉孩子们  健康才是最美的
I think we should be telling our kids it's fine as long as they're healthy.
当然  你只有90磅是因为这样更健康吗
Right. You weigh 90 pounds because it makes you healthier?
算了
Forget it.
他只是觉得要滚蛋的是他  所以心情不好
He's just cranky because he knows he's the one who's gonna get the ax.
有想法了吗
So, any thoughts?
什么  沙龙[以色列总理]对加沙的政策吗
On what? Sharon's plan for Gaza?
你要炒谁鱿鱼
Who you gonna let go?
我想我可以说服沃格勒
I'm thinking I can convince Vogler
把他们全留下最划算
it would be more cost-efficient to keep all of them.
好吧  你可能会搞定他
Yeah, you should be able to pull that off.
大部分亿万富翁都没什么数学头脑
Most billionaires aren't very good with numbers.
如果我可以摸卡梅隆的屁股
It will be more cost-efficient once I grab Cameron's ass,
叫福曼黑桃小子  肯定更划算
call Foreman a spade,
还有奇斯  我也要摸他屁股
and Chase- Well, I'll grab his ass too.
你在很多领域都相当杰出
You are uniquely talented in many areas,
但不包括办公室政治
but office politics is not one of them.
别和沃格勒较量
Don't take Vogler on.
-分开付还是一起  -一起
- Separate or together? - Together.
血糖每分钟上升6.9毫克
Increasing glucose to 6.9 milligrams per minute.
-你还好吗  -我很渴
- Are you okay? - I'm thirsty.
再忍一小会儿就完事了
Just a little bit longer, and you'll be done.
就像奇斯医生
Like Dr. Chase.
赌一把吗
Wanna put some money on it?
我说了我渴
I said I'm thirsty.
再忍五分钟  好吗  甜心
Just five more minutes.Okay, sweetheart?
我不是你的甜心  别那么叫我
I'm not your sweetheart. Don't call me that.
杰西卡  那样说不礼貌
Jessica, that's not nice.
他们这样做才不好
They're the ones who aren't nice.
杰西卡
Jessica.
你也不是好人  我忍不下去了
You're not, either. I don't wanna do this anymore.
杰西卡  杰西卡
Jessica. Jessica,
你要冷静
you have to calm down.
不  不
No.! No.!
放开我
Let me go.
检测血糖浓度  她出现低血糖症了
Check her blood sugar. She's gotta be getting hypoglycemic.
我从没见过她这样  肯定有问题
I've never seen her like this before. Something's wrong.
放开我  把它拿开
Let go of me! Get it out of me!
放开我  你们这些婊子养的  混蛋
Let go of me, you son of a bitch! You bastard!
不
Oh, no.
给她用了镇静剂
She's sedated.
不用担心  斯密斯太太
Mrs. Simms, don't worry.
低血糖症可以导致暂时性精神病
Hypoglycemia can cause temporary psychosis
是高胰岛素正血糖钳夹检测的常见并发症
and is a common complication during an H.E.C. Procedure.
我原本就不想做那个实验
I never wanted it done in the first place.
我们能理解你心情不好
We understand you're upset
你们本来应该维护好她的状况
You were supposed to be monitoring her condition,
可事实你们却在斗嘴打赌
but instead you were bickering and placing bets.
我很抱歉   如果我们让你觉得
I apologize if it looked like
没有全心全意关注你的女儿
we weren't devoting our full attention to your daughter,
但我可以向你保证
but I assure you
拜托了
Oh, please.
省省你的虚情假意  说给你男朋友听吧
Save your pathetic insincerity for your boyfriend.
你错了  她  实际上
You're wrong. She is, in fact,
是绝对真诚的
pathetically sincere.
而且他们也没有搞砸
And they didn't screw it up.
-你是谁  -我从实验室来
- Who are you? - I'm from the lab.
血检结果说明你女儿不是低血糖症
The blood tests show your daughter was not hypoglycemic,
那意味着她的精神病
which means her psychosis
不是某个医生的治疗导致的
wasn't caused by anything these doctors did.
-那么什么原因呢  -我不知道
- So then what was it caused by? - I've no idea.
不过我想你会很高兴得知
But you'll be happy to hear
不能靠节食或运动治疗她
it cannot be cured by diet or exercise.
还有什么能让10岁的女孩怒不可遏呢
What else could cause uncontrollable rage in a 10-year-old?
没什么还能同时引发心脏病的
Nothing that could also cause a heart attack.
我想不用挑明了
I assume I don't have to point out
现在是个绝佳的时机
that now would be an extremely good time
你们中的某一个
for one of you to
可以用一个绝妙的想法让自己脱颖而出
distinguish yourself with a brilliant idea.
血液高凝状态可以引起血栓
A hypercoagulable state can cause a blood clot.
血栓可以导致心脏病
Blood clots can cause a heart attack.
更可能导致中风  胆不是精神病
More likely to cause a stroke, not the psychosis.
不  你错了
No, you're wrong.
如果栓子随血液进入到大脑扁桃腺
If a clot made it to the amygdala area of the brain,
就可能引发无法控制的狂怒
it might cause uncontrollable rage.
不错  一切皆有可能
Right, because anything's possible,
但不会有东西能引起这个年龄孩子出现多发性血栓
but nothing's gonna cause multiple clots in a kid this age.
-她胖  -肥胖症不会导致血栓
- She's fat. - Obesity doesn't cause blood clots.
极度肥胖的病人可能脂肪栓
Extremely obese patients can get a fat embolus.
是的  吸脂手术失败后
Right, after they've had liposuction,
很明显她没做过
which she's clearly never had.
你怎么知道
How do you know?
因为我们有她的医疗记录
Because we have her medical records,
而且没有哪个精神正常的整形医生
and because no plastic surgeon in his right mind is
会给10岁的孩子做吸脂
gonna give a 10-year-old liposuction.
你见过正常的整形医生吗
Have you ever met a plastic surgeon who was in their right mind?
-她没做过吸脂  -谢谢
- She hasn't had liposuction. - Thank you.
那其它荒唐的减肥治疗呢
But what about some other ridiculous obesity treatment?
比如
Like what?
减肥药可以导致心脏病和血栓
Diet pills can cause heart attacks and blood clots.
她的药物毒性分析结果阴性
Her tox screen was negative.
不能说明没用过非处方减肥药
Wouldn't show over-the-counter weight loss drugs.
她妈妈不会让她吃减肥药的
Her mother wouldn't give her diet pills.
她觉得她的女儿这样很完美
She thinks her daughter's perfect just the way she is.
她在撒谎
She's lying.
好吧  你们两个
Okay. You two,
给她用肝素和华法林防止再次栓塞
heparin and warfarin to prevent further clotting.
而你负责找出她吃什么药
And you find those pills.
不是减肥药
Not diet pills.
你最好扩大一点搜索范围
You might wanna broaden the search just a little.
还有  别只问那个妈妈
And don't just ask the mom.
如果她没有提起过  那她...
If she hasn't mentioned it yet, she's not-
如果你要炒什么人  炒就好了
If you're gonna fire someone, go ahead and do it.
别把我们当成是小白鼠
But don't treat us like lab rats,
考验多久后我们会开始相互残杀
testing how long it takes to get us at one another's throats.
-那我该怎么做  -我才不管你怎么做
- So what should I do? - I don't give a damn what you do.
是啊  我早就发现你对此非常冷漠
Yes, I had noticed your complete indifference.
你甚至都不再提诊断建议了
You don't even offer a medical opinion anymore.
-你会炒谁  -我可没那个权力
- Who would you fire? - Not my call.
我想听听你的意见
I want your opinion.
好  那就炒你
Fine, it's you.
说还是不说  你决定吧
Either way, you're making a choice.
奇斯
Chase.
因为他一个月前搞砸了一根血管
Because he screwed up an angio a month ago?
任何人都会犯错
Anyone can make a mistake.
好吧  那就是因为钱了
Right. So it's the money.
你羡慕嫉妒恨
You resent it,
却还跟我说他不需要这份工作
but you're gonna tell me that he doesn't need the job.
他不珍惜这份工作
He doesn't appreciate the job.
为了工作他打算和卡梅隆大战三个回合
He was ready to go three rounds with Cameron for it.
他想要这份工作  他只是不珍惜
He wants the job. He just doesn't appreciate it.
混日子本身没什么错
There's nothing wrong with just wanting to hang out,
但这里不是混日子的地方
but this is not the place to do it.
-我很吃惊  -你以为我会选卡梅隆
- I'm surprised. - You thought I'd pick Cameron?
我以为你谁都不会选
I didn't think you'd pick at all.
早猜到他不是"与世无争"的人
Guess he's not the "Rise above the fray" Guy
他只是希望别人认为他是
he'd like us to think he is.
实际是你逼他选的
You practically forced it out of him.
和其他人一样  他也害怕被炒
He's scared of losing his job, just like everybody else.
我一直在想  你表现得你很可悲
I've been thinking. You've made it quite clear that you're miserable here.
-我不可悲  -你不开心
- I am not miserable. - You're not happy.
-那你呢  -对于工作来说我很开心
- And you are? - With my job, yes.
我在我喜欢的地方  做我想做的事情
I am exactly where I wanna be, doing exactly what I wanna do.
我想我嗅到了一丝醋意
Think I sense a hint of sarcasm there.
你怎么不选自己呢  辞职
Why don't you pick yourself? Quit?
我错了
Hmm, I was wrong.
关于沃格勒还是福曼么
About Vogler or Foreman?
贺尔南德斯太太的孕检
Mrs. Hernandez's pregnancy test.
谁是贺尔南德斯太太
Who's Mrs. Hernandez?
一个怀了外星宝宝的女人或着是你的最新病人
Either a woman carrying an alien baby or your newest patient.
所以说你从没见过她吃药
So you never saw her with any pills.
她从没提到过什么吗
She never mentioned anything?
没有  当然没有
No, of course not.
请问如果我...
Would it be all right if I,
和她的朋友聊聊  方不方便呢
uh, talk to a couple of her friends?
-她的朋友  -我不是要审问他们
- Her friends? - I'm not gonna interrogate them.
我只想问问杰西卡有没有提起过什么
I just wanna ask if Jessica ever mentioned anything.
这  这很重要  她病得很重
It's- It's pretty important. She's very sick.
我明白  只是  好吧
I understand. It's just, well
杰西卡真的没有什么朋友
Jessica really doesn't have any friends.
-一个也没有吗  -我试着帮过她
- Not one? - I've tried to help,
想让孩子们多和她玩玩  可孩子们
make the kids include her more, but... kids can be
-孩子们  -我本想说小混蛋
- Kids? - I was gonna say jerks.
五年级学生和八年级学生结对子
All the fifth-graders are assigned an eighth-grade buddy.
或许你可以找她的搭档谈谈
Maybe you could talk to hers.
豪斯那边怎样
What's the status on House?
他需要时间完成对他每个组员的绩效考核
He asked for time to complete performance reviews for everyone in his department.
你对他说不  然后给了他多长时间
And you told him no and gave him how long?
一个星期  他会搞定的
A week. He'll do it.
那家伙从不屈服于命令
Guy's never done what he's told.
我不觉得他会展开实际行动
I don't see why he's gonna start now.
你好  我是爱德华·沃格勒
Hi. Edward Vogler.
豪斯是不是说我逼他炒了你们中一个
Is Dr. House claiming that i'm forcing him to get rid of one of you?
我打赌他的目的是想煽动你们和我对着干
I assume his goal is to stir up antagonism toward me.
-那你的目的是  -我是在给他施压
- And your goal is? - I am forcing him.
不管他选了谁
I'll do whatever I can to
我会尽我所能帮那个人度过过渡期
ease the transition for whoever he chooses.
如果你有负罪感  有个简单的解决办法
If you're feeling guilty about your decision, there is an easy solution.
我没有负罪感
I don't feel guilty.
那么  为什么跟我说这些
Then... why approach me and tell me all this?
我没有负罪感  那不代表我不内疚
I don't feel guilty. That doesn't mean I don't feel bad.
我有钱  但我还是个人
I'm rich, but I'm still human.
我只希望你能明白
I just wanted you to know
如果有什么能帮你的  可以随时来找我
that if there's anything I can do for you, my door's open.
谢谢
Thank you.
你在收集情报吗
You're lookin' for info?
我以为你早就对豪斯了如指掌
Thought you already had House all figured out.
是的  但还不了解他的团队
I do. Don't know his team though.
B超和活检证明了我们的担忧
The ultrasound and biopsy confirmed our worry.
肿瘤极大  至少有30磅
The tumor is extremely large, at least 30 pounds.
上帝
Oh, God.
实际上是这家医院的个人纪录
It's actually a personal record for this clinic.
不过完全良性  没有任何癌变的迹象
But it's completely benign. There's no sign of cancer at all.
我已经和博金医生谈过了  他上午有空
I've already spoken with Dr. Bergin, and he's available first thing in the morning.
做什么
For what?
做手术
For the surgery.
可如果它不是癌  我不会死  对吧
But if it's not cancer, it can't kill me, right?
-是的  -而我会有一个大疤
- Mmm, no. - I'll have a huge scar.
我就不能再穿比基尼了
I won't be able to wear a bikini.
-你现在穿比基尼吗  -是  你有意见吗
- You wear a bikini now? - Yeah. You got a problem with that?
没有  不过我不会跟你去游泳的
Nope. But I've never gone swimming with you.
我明白了  我知道是怎么一回事了
I knew it. That's what this is all about.
你们想逼我做整形手术
You are trying to force me to have cosmetic surgery.
是啊  所以我在你卵巢上
That's exactly why I planted
种了个30磅肿瘤
a 30-pound tumor on your ovary.
肿瘤不会害死我
It's not gonna kill me.
手术将改变的唯一东西就是我的身材
The only thing surgery is gonna do is change the way I look.
那就是整形手术的意义
That is the definition of cosmetic surgery.
手术也能让你不再烧心和不舒服
Uh, it would also relieve your heartburn and discomfort.
是的  没错
Yeah, right.
把人切开变得让你看来舒服点的话
Why give an antacid if you can cut someone up and
你们又怎么会开抗酸药呢
make them a little easier on your eyes?
我的丈夫
My husband
爱死了我的身体  欲罢不能
loves my body. He can't get enough of it.
你觉得如果我看起来像是条开膛破肚的鱼
You think he's gonna wanna touch me if
他还想碰我吗
I look like I've been gutted like a fish?
真出乎意料
That was unexpected.
没错
Yeah, it was.
课间她只会围着操场不停地跑
All she does during recess is run laps around the playground.
她说那是在运动
She says she's exercising,
不过所有人都知道那是因为没人和她玩
but everyone knows it's just because no one wants to play with her.
我意思是
I mean,
我是她拍档只因为埃尔斯老师让我俩结对子
I'm only her buddy because Ms. Ayers assigned her to me.
但不意味着我是她朋友
That does not mean I am her friend.
我会告知让她的医生们
I'll make sure her doctors are all clear on that.
谢谢
Thanks.
那么  她有和你说起过减肥药吗
So, has she ever said anything to you about diet pills?
她也和你说了吗
Ha. She told you that too?
什么意思
What do you mean?
有一天我撞见她在吃药
I totally busted her for taking drugs one day.
她撒谎  说那是她妈妈给他的减肥药
She totally lied, said that they were diet pills her mom had given her.
够了  现实点
Come on. Get real.
她那样的女孩不可能吃减肥药
No way a girl like that is taking diet pills.
我没有给她减肥药  永远不会
I didn't give her diet pills. I would never do that.
没错  那么就是她想象中的妈妈
Right. So it was her imaginary mom.
她没吃任何药  那女孩撒谎
She didn't take any pills. The girl's lying.
她为什么要撒谎
Why would she lie?
因为她也是个卑鄙的小混蛋
Because she's another mean little jerk.
-妈妈  -对不起  宝贝
- Mom. - I'm sorry, honey.
克雷米没有撒谎
Clemmie didn't lie.
是我撒谎了  我吃过减肥药
I did. I took the pills.
我告诉她是你给的  因为我不想惹麻烦
I told her you gave them to me because I didn't wanna get in trouble.
你从哪搞来的
Where did you get them?
从商店
I took them from the store.
为什么  为什么这么做
Why? Why would you do that?
因为我不想那么丑
Because I didn't wanna be ugly anymore.
-宝贝  你不丑  -不  我丑
- Oh, baby. You're not ugly. - Yes, I am.
我知道你不这样想  但我是  丑极了
I know you don't think so, but I am. I'm disgusting.
杰西卡  求你不要那么说
Jessica, please don't say that.
我就是  我就是想融入大家
I just- I just wanted to fit in.
你明白吗  有朋友
You know, have friends?
或者至少有一个同龄人能对我友好些
Or at least have one person my age be nice to me.
听着
Listen, the, uh-
减肥药导致血栓  心脏病发和失眠
The pills cause blood clots, heart attacks and insomnia.
解释了所有
It explains everything.
我们会观察一晚来确诊
We'll keep her overnight to make sure,
不过  她会没事的
but, uh, she'll be fine.
谢谢
Thank you.
我无法相信她那么绝望
I can't believe she was that desperate.
是啊  我确定要是所有人都讨厌我
Yeah, I'm sure that if everyone I knew hated me,
忍受不了看我  我可不会去商店偷东西
couldn't bear to look at me, I wouldn't go so far as to shoplift.
我不是指偷东西的事
I'm not talking about the shoplifting.
我相信她根本不知道那有多危险
I'm sure she didn't even know they were dangerous.
她可能在电视或网上看了广告
She probably saw them advertised on TV or over the Internet.
没错  我猜  现在又是媒体和药厂的错
Right. So I guess it's the media and pharmaceutical companies' fault now,
而不是她毫不控制暴饮暴食
not the fact that she can't stop shoveling food down her throat.
没人逼她长胖
No one forced her to get fat.
没人强迫癌症病人得癌
No one forced a cancer patient to get cancer.
饶了我吧  这不是病
Give me a break. It's not a disease.
-看了最新的研究吗  -是  看了
- Have you seen the latest research? - Yes, I have.
最近没看到孩子吃苹果或骑自行车
What I haven't seen lately is a kid eating an apple or riding a bike.
你们美国人甚至在篮球上都无法与世界抗衡了
You Americans can't even compete with the rest of the world in basketball anymore,
当然  除非
unless, of course,
是用遥控器在大屏幕上玩的那种
it's the type you play with a remote control on a big-screen TV.
-没错  -等等  等等
- Right. - Wait, wait, wait.
你就打算让他那么说下去吗
Are you gonna let him say that?
他在鄙视咱们的篮球队
He insulted our basketball teams.
老天
Oh, my God.
疼死了
It hurts so bad.
怎么了
What happened?
-她在出血  -哪里
- She's bleeding. - From where?
上帝啊
Oh, my gosh.
求求你们帮帮我
Just please stop it. Please!
减肥药不会导致皮肤坏死
Diet pills don't cause skin necrosis
可能是和药物有关的
Could be something related to the pills
-或者不是  -或两者兼有
- Or not  - Or both
减肥药把她带到我们这里
Diet pills brought her to us.
我们给了她皮肤溃疡
We gave her the sores.
你觉得是她在这里感染了葡萄球菌吗
You think she got a staph infection from something here?
我没说是医院给的皮肤溃疡
I am not saying the hospital gave the sores
我说我们干的  因为治疗
I'm saying we did, by treating her.
华法令导致皮肤坏死
Warfarin-induced skin necrosis.
极度不可能  用华法令前我们用了肝素
Highly unlikely. We started her on heparin before the warfarin.
谁给的肝素
Who gave her the heparin?
我给的华法令  她给的肝素
I did warfarin. She did heparin.
确定你们两个没有都给华法令吗
Sure you didn't both give her warfarin?
确定  我没搞错
Yes. I did not screw up.
你有亲眼看到她准备并给了肝素吗
Did you actually see her prepare and administer the heparin?
不用多说了
Nuff said.
你当时就站在那里
You were standing right there.
我在准备我自己的针剂
I was preparing my own dose.
是啊  没错  应该有其它原因的
Yeah, right. There's gotta be some other cause.
我一个都想不出来
None that I can think of.
让我们纠正错误吧
Let's fix the mistake.
给她用普通静注肝素和
Give her unfractionated I. V. Heparin and
低分子量肝素  立即皮下注射
low molecular weight heparin by subcutaneous injection, stat.
把我弄得难堪不等于能保住你的工作
Making me look bad is not gonna save your job.
你觉得你不可能犯错吗
You think you're incapable of making a mistake?
你以为我会不了了之吗
You think that I'm just gonna roll over and take this?
豪斯不会因为你拍马屁而保你的
House isn't gonna protect you just because you kiss his ass.
沃格勒想帮我
Vogler wants to know what he can do for me.
别在那战战兢兢了  赶紧去看病人吧
Stop worrying about your asses and start worrying about the patient's.
她睡着了么
She sleeping?
镇静剂的作用  不能让她醒着  太疼
As a result of the sedatives, yeah. Can't let her wake up. Too much pain.
华法令诱使皮肤坏死
"Warfarin-induced skin necrosis."
我不明白是什么意思
I... have no idea what that means.
不过这里写着我们给她用了华法令
But it says here we gave her the warfarin.
我还知道"诱使"的意思  是我们的过失吗
And I do know what "Induced" Means. We did this?
眼下看  还不明确
At this point, it's not exactly clear.
你或许该和豪斯医生谈
You should probably talk to Dr. House.
哦  你们两个得花时间把故事编圆了
Oh. You two need time to get your stories straight.
他没告诉我要干什么
He doesn't tell me what to do.
那么你没有只是盲目执行他的命令
So you don't just blindly follow his commands.
你有主张
You're your own man.
可是你在这里
And yet here you are,
为一个你无法忍受的人工作
working for a guy you can't stand.
-我尊敬他  -你到底尊敬他什么
- I respect him. - What exactly is it you respect?
他对人性的态度吗
His attitude toward humanity?
他觉得我们都是傻瓜  说谎成性
He thinks we're all idiots and liars.
他对你的态度呢
How about his attitude toward you?
耍你就像用线球逗小猫
Plays with you like a cat with a ball of string.
你想干吗
What do you want?
我想知道你是否想保住自己的工作
I wanna know if you wanna keep your job.
要是他选择解雇我  我能接受
If he chooses to let me go, I can live with that.
-这不是回答  -你想保我吗
- That's not an answer. - Are you offering to protect me?
-仍不是回答  -我要我的工作
- Still not an answer. - I want my job.
-奇斯医生  -老板
- Dr. Chase. - Boss.
那是怎么回事
What was that about?
他想知道华法令是什么  不清楚
He wanted to know what warfarin is. I don't know.
冻死了
Brr. Icy.
在再次纠正你的错误前  我绝对会三思
I'll definitely think twice before correcting one of your mistakes again.
尽管纠正
Correct all you want.
当然  若真有错的话  就更有效了
Of course, it's a bit more productive if there's an actual mistake.
没错  我老忘了这个
Right. I always forget that part.
我给她用了肝素
I gave her the heparin,
也就是说坏死不是华法令导致的
which means the necrosis is not a reaction to the warfarin,
恐怕也是为何她对你的治疗没有反应的原因
which is probably why she's not responding to your treatment.
目前还没
Yet.
要是你没搞错  那么是什么缘故
If you didn't screw up, then what is it?
-你不知道答案  -目前还没
- You don't have an answer. - Yet.
要是你有了什么想法  告诉我
When you come up with something, let me know.
我在门诊  去暖和暖和
I'll be in the clinic, warming up.
你出问题的时候
I'm the only one who's always stood behind you
我总是唯一那个支持你的人
when you've screwed up.
为什么你要支持一个总出问题的家伙
Why? Why would you support someone who screws up?
因为我没有疯狂的不安全感
Because I'm not insanely insecure,
也因为我能真正的信任另一个人类
and because I can actually trust in another human being,
我不是个愤怒的  憎恶人类的混蛋
and I am not an angry, misanthropic son of a bitch.
抱歉  你说你不愤怒的
I'm sorry. You said you weren't angry.
你会解雇谁
Who would you fire?
谁也不解雇
No one.
没有这个选项
Not an option.
要是大家减薪  延长工作时间
If everyone took a pay cut and put in a few more hours,
我们都能留下  用同样的预算
we could all stay for the same amount of money.
料到你会试着想办法不伤害别人
Figures you'd try and come up with a solution where no one gets hurt.
问题是
The problem is,
世界总是不会如你所愿的
the world doesn't work that way just 'cause you want it to.
料到你会逃避问题
Figures you'd stall and refuse to deal with the issue.
问题是
Problem is,
世界也不会因你逃避而如你所愿的
the world doesn't go away just because you want it to.
打扰了  是豪斯医生吗
Excuse me. Dr. House?
我妻子昨天见过你  露西尔·贺尔南德斯
My wife saw you yesterday. Lucille Hernandez?
他今天不在
Uh, he's not in today.
我妻子说他拄拐杖
My wife said he walked with a cane.
他还有吸毒的毛病
He's also got a bit of a drug problem.
有时候几周不见人
Sometimes doesn't show up for weeks.
核磁共振是租的  不过
The M.R.I. 's are rented, but, um-
-决定了吗  -他不会解雇任何人的
- Did you make a decision? - He's not gonna fire anybody.
对  我们四个都减薪
Yes. I'm gonna cut the pay of all four of us.
减薪17%能让你留住我们全部
Seventeen percent across the board will
能让你用同样的预算留住我们全部
allow you to keep us all for the same amount of money.
我相信这就是你们生意人说的"双赢"
I believe it's what you suits call a "Win-win".
-行  我  要是你能...  -不
- All right, uh, I-if you can... - No.
要是他能接受
If he can work it
那么我们用同样的预算保留现有人员
so we keep the current staff for the same amount of money,
有什么不同吗
what difference does it make?
不是关于钱
It's not about the money.
这不是谈判  从来不是
This is not a negotiation. It never was.
我得知道  无论我让你做什么
I need to know that whatever I ask you to do,
无论你觉得多么不愉快  你都会做
however distasteful you find it, you'll do it.
同样重要的是  你得明白这点
And just as importantly, you need to know that.
我妻子怎么了
What's going on with my wife?
就算我是豪斯医生
Even if I was Dr. House,
医患保密协定允许我不必非得答话
physician-patient confidentiality protects me from annoying conversations.
-她和我说了瘤的事  -是吗
- She told me about the tumor. - Yeah?
她还说了她拒绝摘除手术的原因
She also tell you why she's refusing to have it removed?
我不在乎疤痕
I don't care about a scar.
她还会胖回来的
And she can always gain the weight back.
你要她胖回来吗
You want her to regain the weight?
对  我是说  只要她愿意
Yeah. I mean, only if she wants to.
为什么
Why?
我总是认为她怀孕的时候最性感
I've always thought she looked sexiest when she was pregnant.
知道她是个母亲就让我想要...
Something about knowing she's a mother just makes me want to
和她说  别烦我
Tell her that and leave me alone.
我说了  你得和她谈谈
I did. You gotta talk to her.
要是她有什么不测  我没法忍受
I couldn't bear it if something happened to her.
瘤是良性的  什么也不会发生
The tumor is benign. Nothing's gonna happen,
除了有点烧心
except maybe some more heartburn.
要是它变大呢  或者癌变了
What if it gets even bigger, or it changes?
你知道去哪找我们  这座楼是不会跑走的
You know where to find us. Building's not going anywhere.
告诉她是癌症  显然你撒谎很在行
Tell her it's cancer. You obviously don't have a problem with lying.
想法说服我
Oh. Way to win me over.
我们有6个孩子  她不能有侥幸心理
We got six kids. She can't afford to take a chance.
你们有孩子  多新鲜啊
You have kids. How novel.
那样的话就不一样了
That changes everything.
要是妈妈烧心了  其中一个就着火了
So if Mommy gets heartburn, one of them might catch on fire.
求你  我不知道我们该怎么办
Please. I don't know what we do.
他们很可爱
They are cute.
-让她回来  -什么
- Have her come back in. - What?
你的境况打动了我  让你妻子回来
Your plight has moved me. Tell your wife to come back.
坏死情况更严重了
The necrosis is getting worse.
可能是我们找错病因了
Maybe because we're treating her for the wrong thing.
-那你找到真正的病因了吗  -没有
- Have you found the right thing? - No.
那就接着治疗
Then we continue the treatment,
希望只是时间问题
hope it's just taking longer than it should.
现在  是什么引起细胞坏死已不重要了
At this point, it doesn't matter what caused the necrosis.
-或者是谁  -若我们不阻止它扩散的话
- Or who. - If we don't stop it from spreading,
她撑不到明天
it'll kill her before the end of the day.
-我们还能做什么  -除掉它
- What else can we do?  - Get rid of it.
在坏死肌肉
Remove the dying flesh
穿透腹壁前除掉它
before it penetrates the abdominal wall.
照做吧
Do it.
肝素治疗还是有可能
There's still a chance the heparin treatment
会起作用
could start to take effect.
我们会尽量等
We're gonna wait as long as we can,
但若接下来的几小时内仍无好转的话
but if there's no change in the next few hours,
我们只能直接对病患进行手术了
we're gonna have to treat the symptoms directly.
-你们能去除溃疡吗  -通过外科手术
- So you can get rid of the sores? - Through surgery.
基本来说  就是切除术
technically, it's an amputation.
切除术  但溃疡是...
Amputation? But the sores are-
华法林导致的坏死细胞攻击脂肪组织
Warfarin-induced necrosis attacks fatty tissue,
主要是乳房
mainly in the breasts.
等等  你是说要割除
Wait. Are you talking about cutting off
我女儿的  乳房
my daughter's... breasts?
她才10岁
She's 10 years old.
乳房切除术可能是她生存的唯一希望了
A radical mastectomy may be her only chance for survival.
很抱歉  但还得请你在这上面签字
I'm sorry, but I'm gonna have to ask you to sign this.
我们能谈谈吗
Could we talk?
怎么  没玫瑰  没巧克力
What, no roses, no chocolates?
-若你是来道歉的  -我不是来道歉的
- If you're here to apologize... - I'm not here to apologize.
看来事情还没那么简单
That means you're here for something more complicated.
你想炒了我吗
Do you want to fire me?
是的  只等恰当的时机了
Yes. Just waiting for an excuse.
谁让沃格勒出现了呢
Thank God Vogler came along.
只有这能解释你为什么
It's the only reason I can think of
坚持说我犯了错
why you're insisting that I made a mistake.
是吗  还有另一种解释啊
Really? Because there is another explanation.
可能没你那个弗洛伊德式的分析有趣
Perhaps not as much fun as your Freudian analysis,
但也许你确实犯了错
but maybe you actually made a mistake.
这样做是因为你无法控制
You're doing this because you can't deal with
对我的感情
your feelings for me.
是你在一厢情愿吧
I believe that you are the only one to express feelings.
从一个刚入门的心理医生
And if we're gonna look at this from
的角度来看的话
a first-year psych's point of view,
也许是你想让我炒了你
maybe you want me to fire you.
所以你才表现的很奇怪
Maybe that's why you're acting weird
你才奇怪呢
You're the one being different.
你总是在施压  压迫规则
You're always pushing things, pushing the rules,
压迫我们  但这次却没有
pushing us. But not this time.
你像看到救命稻草一样死抓住那个诊断
You jumped on this idea like a life raft.
一点不怀疑可能是别的病
Not one question about what else it could be.
不追问其他答案
No riding us for other answers.
我知道答案
I have the answer.
那你干嘛不看看电视
Then why aren't you watching TV
玩玩混账的掌上游戏
or playing your damn Game Boy...
或者无论什么你能独乐乐的事情呢
or whatever else you have so much fun doing by yourself?
也许是我该退出
Maybe I should just quit.
让大家都好过
Make it easy for everyone.
也许你确实该如此
Maybe you should.
男人是蠢猪
Men are pigs.
你把我叫来就为了告诉我
You called me in to tell me-
我竟没注意到结扎和避孕套
I should've realized the vasectomy and condoms
是万无一失的
was overkill,
但这个就不容忽视了
but this was too obvious to miss.
可爱的孩子
Cute kids.
我爱死她的绿眼睛和他的蓝眼睛
Love her green eyes and his baby blues.
当然  因为你和你丈夫
Of course, since both you and your husband
是棕色眼睛
have brown eyes-
你从哪儿拿到的
Where'd you get that?
是其中三个
From the father of three,
最多四个孩子是爸爸生的
maximum four, of your six children.
所以我猜  你不想做手术的原因也许是
So I'm thinking maybe the reason you don't want surgery...
尽管不论变成啥样  你丈夫
is that while your husband will find you attractive
都不会嫌弃你
no matter what,
但和你有关系的其他男人
all the other men you're sleeping with
可没那么大度
might not be so open-minded.
也回归了我最初的定论  男人是蠢猪
Which brings me back to my original thesis: Men are pigs.
你没必要担心
You got nothing to worry about.
他们可能和任何人做爱
They'll pretty much have sex with anyone:
胖的  瘦的  已婚的  单身的
Fat, skinny, married, single,
陌生的  亲戚
complete strangers, relatives-
-你有病  -你也是
- You... are sick.  - So are you.
网上肯定有一堆的男人
And I'm sure there are Web Sites full of men...
喜欢有手术疤痕的已婚妇女
Iooking for married women with surgical scars.
接受手术吧  好吗
So have the surgery. Please?
好吧
Okay.
你为什么找卡梅隆谈话
Why have you been talking to Cameron?
如果豪斯选了你
If House picks you,
我得找个新耳目啊
I'll be needing a new source in that room.
如果他选我  怎讲
If he picks me?
当然  福曼比你聪明
Sure. Foreman's smarter.
豪斯很欣赏卡梅隆
House has got a thing for Cameron.
我一直给你提供消息  你得保护我
I've been feeding you information so you'll protect me.
我需要你时自然会保护你
And I will protect you as long as I need you.
只要你需要我  你也得一直提供我消息
And you will feed me information as long as you need me.
我和卡梅隆谈话是因为若有了替代人选
I spoke with Cameron because if I have alternatives,
我就不需要你了
I don't need you.
她不会背叛豪斯的
She's not gonna rat on House.
福曼没提到和我谈过话吗
Foreman never said anything about talkin' to me?
有意思啊
Interesting, huh?
快3个小时了
It's been almost three hours.
还是没任何好转
Still no change in her condition.
我觉得该动手术了
I think we should get her into surgery.
你想怎么做
So what do you wanna do?
假如卡梅隆没错
Assume that Cameron didn't screw up.
万一不是华法林的问题呢
What if it's not the warfarin?
只可能是这原因
It has to be.
我们一用华法林她就出现了溃疡
The sores presented right after we administered it.
是的  没错  但就假设不是
Right, right, right. But let's just say it's not.
快想  快想  还有其他可能没
Come on. Come on. What do you got?
能给点时间想一下吗
Can I have a second to think?
不行  没时间了
No. There's no time to think.
说出你脑子里的第一反应
Just say the first thing that comes into your head.
她很胖
She's fat.
够了好吗  我们知道  你讨厌胖人
Enough already, okay? We got it. You hate fat people.
我不是这个意思
That's not what I meant.
我们已经讨论过那个了
We already considered obesity as a cause.
她的其他医生也是
So did all her other doctors.
不  我是说万一那不是病因
No, I mean what if it's not a cause?
而是病症呢
What if it's a symptom?
好  那什么能引起肥胖和皮肤坏死呢
Okay. So, what could cause obesity and skin necrosis?
不管说不说得通  先给点意见
I don't care if it makes sense. Just give me something.
溃疡继发性血管炎
Ulcers secondary to vasculitis.
不是  那只能引发溃疡  没有坏死
No, that's just sores, not obesity.
-坏疽性脓皮病  -也是溃疡
- Pyoderma gangrenosum. - More sores.
从另一个方面来想
Let's look at it from the other side.
肥胖是什么的病症
What has obesity as a symptom?
-甲状腺功能减退  -更可能是遗传
- Hypothyroidism?  - Genetics are more likely.
她妈妈也很胖
Her mom's heavy too.
她虽胖  但也很高
She's not just heavy, she's tall.
-有没有她爸爸的记录  -有
- We have any history on the dad? - Yeah.
6英尺1英寸[约1米85]
6'1 .
孩子很矮
Kid's short.
她发育迟缓  血压高
We got stunted growth, high blood pressure,
血栓  肥胖
blood clots, obesity-
是库欣病
It's Cushing's.
不可能  那不会引起细胞坏死
No. Necrosis doesn't present-
在少数情况下  库欣病能引发高钙血症
In rare cases, Cushing's can cause hypercalcemia,
它能和华法林一样导致皮肤坏死
which can lead to the same skin necrosis as warfarin.
绝对是的  解释通了所有病症
It's perfect. It explains everything.
但不是库欣病
Except it's not Cushing's.
她已经接受过多项血液检测
She's had multiple blood tests,
但没一个显示皮质醇水平不正常
and none show abnormal cortisol levels.
高钙血症可能是周期性的
The hypercortisolism could be cyclical.
我们没有抓住时机
We didn't catch it in the right phase.
那得再做一次血检
We'll have to do another U.F.C.
没时间了
There's no time.
必须在一小时内做决定
We've got less than an hour to make a call.
若我们按库欣病治疗  结果不是
If we treat for Cushing's and we're wrong,
她就没命了
she's dead.
假若不是库欣病
If we assume it's not Cushing's,
等她的乳房被摘除后还是不行
she'll lose her breast and may still be sick.
做磁共振
Do an M.R.I.
你想用磁共振来检测高钙血症吗
You want us to look for hypercortisolism with an M.R.I.?
不  我是说用磁共振来检查
No, I want you to look for
是什么引发了高钙血症
what could cause hypercortisolism with an M.R.I.
肾上腺没问题
Nothing on the adrenals.
听说卡梅隆回家了  她病了吗
Heard Cameron went home. Is she sick?
返回脑垂体视图
Go back to the pituitary views.
她看起来很好啊
She seemed okay.
那还能有别的原因离开吗
Think she's got another reason for leaving?
希望吧  等等  停
I hope so. Wait, stop.
那里  那是什么
There. What's that?
一个肿瘤
A tumor.
是库欣病
It's Cushing's.
肿瘤引发了库欣病
The tumor causes Cushing's.
库欣病扰乱了荷尔蒙分泌
Cushing's messes with hormone production.
荷尔蒙对各方面都有影响
Hormones control everything:
发育  体重
Growth, weight-
-能治好吗  -需要手术摘除肿瘤
- Can you fix it? - She'll need surgery to remove the tumor.
一旦肿瘤清除  很快一切都会恢复正常
Once it's gone, everything will get normal very fast.
-不需要切除乳房吗  -不需要
- No mastectomy? - No.
-太好了  -手术会有风险
- Thank God. - The surgery is dangerous.
脑下垂体位于海绵状窦之间
The pituitary's located between the cavernous sinuses,
基本上  就是两眼之间
basically right between the eyes.
那里还有控制
The area contains the nerves that control
眼球运动的神经和给大脑供血的主动脉
eye movement and the major arteries that feed the brain.
天哪
Oh, my God.
手术会采用经蝶窦入路法靠近腺体
The surgeon will approach the gland transsphenoidally.
医生会在唇下开个切口
An incision will be made under the lip,
通过那个切口植入一个光纤显微镜
through which he'll insert a fiber-optic microscope.
一旦发现肿瘤  就将它切为
Once the tumor's found, he'll cut it into
碎块  然后再
small pieces and remove it
通过切口取出
through the same hole under the lip.
整个手术需要大概3个小时
The whole procedure should take about three hours,
你女儿应该几天之后
and your daughter should be able to
就可以回家了
go home in a few days.
溃疡  疲乏和
The sores will go away,
肌肉疼痛都会消失
as well as her fatigue and the muscle pain.
她的体重也会下降
She'll even start losing weight.
-杰西卡  -嗨
- Jessica. - Hi.
-真的是你吗  -没错  是我
- Is that really you? - Yep, it's me.
你看起来漂亮极了
You look fantastic.
-她一直都很漂亮  -是的
- She always looked fantastic. - Yeah.
已经一星期了
It's been a week.
事实上  是一个多星期了
Actually, it's over a week.
你们最近好吗
How have you guys been?
是谁
Who is it?
奇斯
Chase.
不行  奇斯留下  另选一个
No, Chase stays. Pick someone else.
-说好了...  -我改变主意了
- The deal was... - The deal's changed.
-再选个人  -不行
- Pick someone else. - No.
再选一个  不然我就炒了整个部门
Pick someone else, or it'll be the whole department.